So I have some news.
I went to the grocery store yesterday and there was a man sitting outside by the fountain and he was hanging his head low.
And I said, you're good?
And he lift up his head and he said, nah, not good, not good.
I said, you're not good?
You're not good?
And he said, nah, nah.
I said, well, what do you need?
He said, food.
I need food.
I said, well, what do you want?
He said, chicken, chicken.
So I said, okay, well, I'll get you some chicken.
So I go in the grocery store and then I couldn't find like already prepared hot food.
So then I came back outside and I said, come in the store with me now.
Come in the store.
So he comes in the store with me and he goes right to it, gets the food.
I said, you want something to drink?
He said, yeah.
So he goes and gets his drink.
But then he proceeds to talk to everybody who works in the store and let them know that he's married now.
So congratulations, guys.
I'm married.
Support a real one.